RICHARD HAN

richard.ly.han@gmail.com

021 025 18876 | richardhan.com



github.com/rlyhan



linkedin.com/in/richard-ly-han

INTRO

I'm a passionate web developer who loves to build innovative solutions that strive to benefit society. I have developed strong problem solving abilities. a fast learning pace, and coding proficiency from studying for over 4 years.

My strengths lie in developing full stack web projects using JavaScript and an array of technologies, planning and delivering software using Agile methodologies, and working in a team environment.

PROJECTS

FORAGED AND FOUND

- foraged-and-found.herokuapp.com
- Site for the foraging community to help them find and share foragable items on a Google
- Technologies: React, Redux, Bootstrap, Node. JS, SQLite

WELLY

- explore-welly.herokuapp.com
- Site for finding popular restaurants, bars, shops and more in Wellington, New Zealand
- Technologies: React, Redux, Bootstrap, Node. JS, MongoDB

EDUCATION

ENSPIRAL DEV ACADEMY

2019 - 2019 | Full Stack Web Development

UNIVERSITY OF CANTERBURY

2017 - 2019 | Computer Science

VICTORIA UNIVERSITY OF WELLINGTON

2015 - 2016 | Computer Science | Architecture

ST. ANDREW'S COLLEGE

2006 - 2014 | Secondary education Senior College Diploma | Dean's Academic Top 40

SKILLS

PRIMARY SKILLSET

My strongest skills, learned during my time at Enspiral Dev Academy and through Treehouse, used to develop full stack web projects.

NODE.JS JAVASCRIPT HTML SQL **CSS MONGODB** REACT **GIT REDUX DEPLOYMENT BOOTSTRAP TESTING**

OTHER LANGUAGES/FRAMEWORKS

Learned during my time at university.



OTHER SKILLS

PHOTOSHOP: NOVICE INDESIGN: NOVICE

JAPANESE SPEAKER: INTERMEDIATE

CERTIFICATIONS



TREEHOUSE - FULL STACK JAVASCRIPT TECHDEGREE

WORK HISTORY

FARMERS, THE HUB HORNBY

2017 - 2019 | Loss Prevention Associate

MEMORIES OF HONG KONG

2011 - 2017 | Kitchenhand

INTERESTS



MUSICIAN



SKIING



FITNESS